https://www.papercheck.com/about-us/privacy-policy/

Our Commitment to Privacy
Your privacy is important to us. This Privacy Policy applies to https://www.papercheck.com owned and operated by Papercheck, LLC. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.
If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request.
Top of Page
The Information We Collect
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Papercheck website. On some pages, you can order services, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personally identifiable information collected on these pages are:
Name
Address
Email Address
Phone Number
Credit/Debit Card Information
On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you believe Papercheck’s editing and proofreading services would be useful to a friend, you can elect to send our general information to that person via email. Your friend may contact us to request that we remove this information from our database. In this circumstance, the types of personally identifiable information collected are:
Name
Email Address
Phone Number
We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, contact us. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
Top of Page
Choice/Opt-out
When we ask for your personally identifiable information, we provide you the opportunity to “opt out” of having this information used for certain purposes. For example, if you purchase our editing service but do not wish to receive any additional marketing materials from us, you can indicate your preference in your account profile.
We only send out service-related emails as part of our service. You may not opt-out from these emails. If you no longer wish to receive these emails, you may do so by canceling your account with us.
You will be notified when your personally identifiable information is collected by any third party that is not our agent/service provider, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party.
Top of Page
The Way We Use Information
We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.
We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order, fulfill the requested services, and send communications related to our service if you register (for example, we may send a “thank you” package for your patronage or provide a newsletter). We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. Typically, we share with our editors only the information that is necessary for them to proofread your documents.
We use the information you provide about other people when we send information to them. For example, in our “referral” function, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We store this information to track the success of the referrals and send a one-time invitation. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the requested information. We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. Your friend may contact us to request that we remove this information from our database.
Papercheck, LLC and its partners use cookies or similar technologies to analyze trends, administer the website, track users’ movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. You can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level, but if you choose to disable cookies, it may limit your use of certain features or functions on our website or service.
We partner with a third-party ad network to either display advertising on our website or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies or similar technologies to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other websites in order to provide you with targeted advertising based upon your interests. To opt-out of interest-based advertising by participating companies in the following consumer choice mechanisms, please visit:
Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA)’s self-regulatory opt-out page (http://optout.aboutads.info/) and mobile application-based “AppChoices” download page (https://youradchoices.com/appchoices)
European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance (EDAA)’s consumer opt-out page (http://youronlinechoices.eu)
Network Advertising Initiative (NAI)’s self-regulatory opt-out page (http://optout.networkadvertising.org/).
Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.
Like most standard website servers, we use log files. These include data such as Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks. This information allows us to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information, except to prevent fraud.
From time to time, we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary, and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address) and demographic information (such as zip code). We may use a service provider to conduct these surveys or contests for us; that company is not permitted to use personally identifiable information for any other purpose.
In certain situations, Papercheck, LLC may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website, and when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.
If you post a testimonial or blog on this website, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of this site and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit on this site. To request removal of your personally identifiable information from our site, contact us. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personally identifiable information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.
If Papercheck, LLC is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website of any change in ownership or uses of your personally identifiable information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personally identifiable information.
Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
Top of Page
Service Providers
We use Authorize.net and PayPal’s PayFlow Pro to provide credit card processing on our website. When you sign up for editing services, we will share billing information as necessary for the third party to provide that service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.
Links to Other Sites
This website contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Papercheck, LLC. Please be aware that we, Papercheck, LLC, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.
We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy policies of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information.
This privacy policy applies only to information collected by this website.
Social Media Widgets
Our website includes social media features, such as the Facebook button, and widgets, such as the “Share this” button and interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These features may collect your IP address as well as which page you are visiting on our site, and they may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing them.
Our Commitment to Data Security
The security of your personally identifiable information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number and/or Social Security number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). To learn more about SSL, go to http://www.verisign.com.
We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personally identifiable information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personally identifiable information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
If you have any questions about security on our website, you can email us at support@papercheck.com.
Our Commitment to Children’s Privacy
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.
Top of Page
How to Access or Correct Your Information
Upon request Papercheck, LLC will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by logging in to your Papercheck account and clicking on “user profile” over the SSL or secured socket layer. All information sent to https://www.papercheck.com in an SSL session is encrypted, protecting against disclosure to third parties. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.
You can correct or delete factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error through any of our contact details below. You can also update, correct, or delete any of your personally identifiable information on your account by going to your “user profile.” We will respond to your request to access within 30 days.
To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
Top of Page
Changes in This Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy policy, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage before the changes take effect.
How to Contact Us
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 1-866-693-3348 or send us an email.
Mailing Address:
Physical Address:
Alternate Phone Number:
1-415-213-4836
Top of Page
LOGIN
REGISTER
Search for:
April 20, 2015Hello, Papercheck.com. Again, thank you for being prompt with my document, for you guys are amazing. Best always! -Pamela
ABOUT SSL CERTIFICATES
